Daniel Ibragimov

Forest Hills, New York | danny.ibragimov1@gmail.com | 917-499-9679| https://danielibrag.github.io/ github.com/Daniellbrag | linkedin.com/in/daniel-ibragimov/

Full-Stack Software Developer

I am a constant learner who strives to become a talented programmer in as many facets as possible. Previous experience in IT and pharmacy management has given me strong problem-solving abilities and a dedication to mastering fundamentals in order to contribute quickly in new settings.

Skills

Technical: Ruby, Rails, Vue.js, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PostgreSQL, Git, GitHub, APIs, Pair-Programming,

Testing, Object-Oriented Programming, Bootstrap, C++

Additional: Russian (fluent), Adobe Creative Suite, Microsoft Suite

Education

Actualize | Certificate in Full Stack Web Development

January 2022 - May 2022

- Capstone Project (League of Legends Proven Builds and Builder): personally built a web app that pulls from the Riot Games API and database and extracts the highest win rate builds as well as allowing the user to make their own custom builds and saving them on their profile. Built in Ruby on Rails and Vue.is.
- Bootcamp: Learned fundamentals and best practices in full-stack web development in areas of project architecture, backend, frontend, and how to effectively self-teach new technologies
 - Generated technical requirements and determined the most effective solutions, created wireframes, designed schema, and researched outside resources
 - Built and tested the backend, incorporating external APIs
 - Created pages and RESTful routes, made web requests to retrieve data, formatted and styled results, incorporated libraries and themes

Queensborough Community College

2019

Associate of Applied Science in Information Technology and Information Security

Experience

Cort Pharmacy Inc. | Pharmacy Technician/Stock Manager

July 2017 - Present

- Upgraded the entire pharmacy's technical system including computers and server to allow for faster workflow between machines as well as a guicker patient experience at the POS system
- Operated 3 separate pharmaceutical softwares (including OPUS RX30 and Datascan) to efficiently read patient profiles and process and fill medications for these patients
- Oversaw the hours and work of 8-10 stock employees and cashiers to optimize for workflow efficiency and staffing costs

Direct Designs | SEO Manager

August 2017 - June 2019

- Wrote bi-weekly blog postings using Wordpress, HTML, and JavaScript for 6 separate businesses spanning multiple industries to increase interaction between business and consumers
- Established an active SEO presence for business using keywords increased rankings and search rates on Google, other search engines, and social media, increasing traffic to their websites and total business
- Operated the social media platforms for these businesses including Facebook and Instagram, routing messages to the correct staff member, reducing response times and improving customer service

The Pavilion Nursing Home and Rehabilitation Facility | Dialysis Assistant June 2016 - August 2017

- Assisted RN's and Dialysis technicians in getting the correct acids and sodium bicarbonates required for each successful dialysis session
- Collaborated with dialysis techs and nurses to transport patients to the dialysis wing of the facility and reduce nurses' workload